galaxyplus.com 2013-12-28

# Fiserv - Privacy Policy

**Last Update Posted: February 10, 2012**

Fiserv, Inc., on behalf of itself and its affiliates, (together, "Fiserv") knows that privacy is important to you. It is also vital to our business. This Privacy Policy describes the types of "Personal Information" (information that is identifiable to a particular person) that Fiserv collects in connection with this Site, as defined in Fiserv’s [Terms and Conditions of Use](http://www.fiserv.com/about/terms.htm) (the “Terms”). Fiserv does not sell or distribute Personal Information to third parties. Fiserv gathers Personal Information and will distribute this information within Fiserv in an effort to meet your needs and respond to your information requests. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) sets forth the guidelines Fiserv uses in protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is considered part of the [Terms](http://www.fiserv.com/about/terms.htm).

**1\. What Types of "Personal Information" We Collect, How We Collect It and How We May Use and Disclose Your Personal Information.** Fiserv collects Personal Information about visitors to this Site indirectly through our Internet access logs. When you access fiserv.com or any other sites, social media pages or other Internet destinations related to Fiserv, your browser's domain name and Internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs. Fiserv uses this information to learn about which pages and information our Site visitors access and how often. Fiserv also collects Personal Information when you directly submit it to us. Throughout this Site, Fiserv provides the opportunity to, among other matters, subscribe to e-mail alerts regarding Fiserv events or company news, to request company information, or to request product or service information through an e-mail contact form. When Fiserv collects Personal Information from you, we intend to use the Personal Information to meet your needs and respond to your requests. It is completely up to you whether to provide this Personal Information. Fiserv may also use and disclose Personal Information in order to comply with laws, regulations, court orders and lawful instructions from a government agencies or other competent authority, to protect the personal safety of users of our services or the public, to defend Fiserv from claims, to resolve disputes, to troubleshoot problems, to enforce the Terms, or to protect Fiserv rights and property.

**2\. Cookies, Browser Information and Related Issues.**

a. When you visit this Site, Fiserv receives certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring website addresses, and other such information. This data may be used among other uses to improve the operation of this Site and to improve Site security by assisting in "authenticating" who you are when you access this Site, particularly if you register for a Site offering or functionality and are issued or create a username and password.

b. Fiserv may also receive additional information about your visit to this Site, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take in connection with this Site and the products and services offered through it. This data may be used among other uses to improve the operation of this Site and to make this Site design more efficient.

c. Like most websites, this Site also uses "cookies," which are small text files placed on your computer by the web server when you visit this Site. Most such cookies are "session" cookies that are only used for a specific period during which you are on this Site, but a few are "persistent" cookies that stay on your hard drive and are read by the web server when you return to this Site. This Site uses cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content on your later visits to this Site. Cookies cannot and will not be used to deliver or run programs on your computer. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of this Site that depend on cookies.

**3\. How We Protect Your Personal Information.** To protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access and use, Fiserv maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards, and require those to whom we disclose Personal Information (including our employees and service providers that assist us in operating this Site) to do the same. 

**4\. External Links.** This Site may provide links to other third party websites. Even if the third party is affiliated with Fiserv through a business relationship or otherwise, Fiserv is not responsible for the conditions or results of use, privacy policies or practices or the content of such external links or the person or entity responsible for them. These links are provided to you for your convenience only, and you access them at your own risk.

**5\. Keeping Up to Date with Our Privacy Policy.** Fiserv may amend this Policy at any time by posting a revised version on this Site, which will be effective at the time it is posted unless a delayed effective date is expressly stated in the revision.

**6\. Other Fiserv Sites.** This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Site, as specified above. However, an Other Fiserv Site (as defined in the [Terms](http://www.fiserv.com/about/terms.htm)) may have its own privacy policy or other privacy-related terms posted. As with the [Terms](http://www.fiserv.com/about/terms.htm), those other privacy terms and conditions shall apply to privacy-related issues regarding that Other Fiserv Site and the use of any services, functionalities or other offerings made in connection with that Other Fiserv Site, and this Privacy Policy shall not apply in such circumstances. Furthermore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any websites Fiserv creates for any individual client, and such websites shall be subject to the terms and conditions set forth in the applicable agreement between Fiserv and that client.

**7\. Contacting Us.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the address specified in the [Terms](http://www.fiserv.com/about/terms.htm).
